SHUBHAM SINGH

ABOUT

I'm a full stack web developer with 1.5 years of experience on Javascript and it's frameworks such as Angular, React, Vue using NodeJS. I'm flexible on using any framework and looking forward to work on projects using these latest technologies.

CONTACT

+91 8126062707 mynameshubham@gmail.com http://18.216.186.17 https://github.com/strcoder4007

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER | ALLPS DIGITAL GMBH | JUN 2018 - PRESENT

I've been working in a Zurich based startup where my responsibility varies for several projects as full stack developer and as frontend developer on some using VueJs, ReactJs, Redux, NodeJs and PHP/Laravel

FULL STACK INTERN | CARTISAN | APR 2018 - JUN 2018

Built a livestream using MEAN stack and Alicloud as the streaming server. Worked with various web video encoders and decoders written in C++ running on nodejs.

INTERN SOFTWARE ENGINEER | WALLFRUIT TECH. | DEC 2016 - MAR 2017

Built a SaaS platform for construction engineers for automating management of their workers, blueprints, materials and progress using MEAN stack.

FEATURED PROJECTS

MEMORY SEQUENCE | ANGULAR 7, EXPRESSIS, TYPESCRIPT, NODEIS

A web app for blogging with everything written from scratch i.e designing, frontend and backend. (http://18.216.186.17/memseq)

LETSCODE.LIVE | REACTJS, REDUX, EXPRESSIS, NODEJS

A webapp made using ReactJS and Redux for displaying all algorithmic contests running across all competitive programming websites. (http://letscode.live)

INSTACODE ONLINE JUDGE | JAVASCRIPT, PHP, BOOTSTRAP

Online platform and judge for holding algorithmic contests (just like hackerrank, codechef etc.)

This website has been used to hold various college contests as well as serve as the official platform for lab practical use in my college. (http://instacode.xyz/)

IONIC MESSENGER | IONIC, ANGULAR, EXPRESSIS, SCOKET.IO

A chat app made for android and iOS for demonstrating obscure features such as going private with another user, giving a specific time to a message etc.

AWARDS

EDUCATION

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR | HACKERRANK | 2016 QUALIFIED ACM ICPC INDIA REGIONALS | 2017 **KIET GROUP OF INSTITUTIONS, 2018**B.TECH,
COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING